ammyy.com 2017-12-11

# Ammyy Admin - Privacy Policy.

### Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Ammyy’s website located at [www.ammyy.com](http://www.ammyy.com/). We are firmly committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. To that end, we are pleased to provide this Privacy Policy to describe our information gathering and use.

**Acquisition of information**

You may visit our site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Our site does collect information such as domain, IP address, browser type and operating system for site trends and statistics, but this information does not personally identify you.

We may ask you to provide personally identifiable information if you are signing up as our reseller and partner. Some information about your company, its size or other details may be required by us via email while providing pre-sale support.

**How we use the information**

The personal information you provide will be used for the purpose for which it was intended - to contact you, to process an order, to register your product, etc. Ammyy may also use any information you have provided as is reasonably necessary to provide customer support to you. Ammyy may also use your contact information to provide notices regarding the products or services that you have purchased, as well as to inform you about new products or promotional campaigns.

**With whom we share your information**

Ammyy may share information with its billing companies. This is necessary for processing and troubleshooting your orders.  
Your information may be shared with Ammyy’s authorized resellers and partners who we may think would serve you better.

**Information Security**

Ammyy will strictly protect the security of your personal information, protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Your personal data, including your e-mail address, is used for internal purposes only and is never sold or shared with anyone outside of Ammyy or our authorized resellers, unless we disclose information in response to a law enforcement request.

**Public Forums**

Public forum is part of the site. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information; we caution you to exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information in forums.
